chromeactions.com 2015-09-24

# Magic Actions for YouTube™ | Privacy Policy

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, products and services, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### What information do we collect?

We can collect information from you when you fill out a support form. Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional.

Like most websites, we use cookies and local storage to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies and local storage?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used to:

• Personalize your experience. Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.

• Improve our website, products and services we have provided to you. We continually strive to improve our website, products and services offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

• Improve customer service. Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

### Do we use cookies and local storage?

Yes. Cookies are small pieces of data that a site or its service provider can save to your computers hard drive through your Web browser, if you allow. [Learn more](http://www.hotcleaner.com/cookie-wiper.html "About Cookies")

Google, as a third party vendor, [uses cookies](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/technologies/cookies/ "Learn more about cookies used by Google") to serve ads and measure how users interact with website content on our site. You may [opt out](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous) of the use of advertising cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

Also, we may collect and store information using [HTML5 local storage](http://www.hotcleaner.com/web_storage.html "Learn more about HTML5 local storage") and application data caches. We can use local storage to compile aggregate data about site traffic, site and apps interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and apps in the future. We do not store any personally identifiable information.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our website, products and services and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act). Our website, products and services are not intended for people under 13 years of age and are not directed at children. We do not knowingly solicit and do not collect personally identifiable information from anyone under 13 years of age.

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.chromeactions.com/terms.html) section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website, products and services.

### Your Consent

By using our website, products and services, you consent to this privacy policy and [terms of use.](http://www.chromeactions.com/terms.html)

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

This policy was last modified on **August 30, 2015**

### Contact US

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us by [email](mailto:support@chromeactions.com) or by filling out the [form](http://www.chromeactions.com/magic-actions-for-youtube-support.html).

Powered by Trust Guard [PCI compliance](http://www.trust-guard.com/) scans.
